{
    "questions_and_answers": [
{
    "question": "When was the Department of Information Science & Engineering established?",
    "answer": "The Department of Information Science & Engineering was established in the year 1999. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Overview"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the initial intake of students in the Department of Information Science & Engineering?",
    "answer": "The initial intake of students in the Department of Information Science & Engineering was 40. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Overview"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many students can the Department of Information Science & Engineering accommodate now?",
    "answer": "The Department of Information Science & Engineering can accommodate 180 students now. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Overview"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of the Information Science course?",
    "answer": "The Information Science course provides a comprehensive understanding of the principles, theories, and practical applications that form the foundation of Information Science. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Overview"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the fields that the Information Science course covers?",
    "answer": "The Information Science course covers the principles, theories, and practical applications of computer science, mathematics, and engineering. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Overview"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the role of Information Science Engineering in the digital world?",
    "answer": "Information Science Engineering plays a pivotal role in the increasingly digitized and interconnected world, influencing the way we communicate, process information, and make decisions. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Overview"
  },
  {
    "question": "What facilities does the Department of Information Science & Engineering provide?",
    "answer": "The Department of Information Science & Engineering provides state-of-the-art facilities for learning, research, and hands-on exploration in the dynamic field of computer science. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Overview"
  },
  {
    "question": "How does the Department of Information Science & Engineering maintain connections with industries?",
    "answer": "The Department of Information Science & Engineering maintains strong connections with industries by facilitating internship opportunities for students. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Overview"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do industry partnerships benefit students?",
    "answer": "Industry partnerships provide students with real-world exposure, bridging the gap between academic learning and industry demands. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Overview"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the track record of the Department of Information Science & Engineering in terms of placement?",
    "answer": "The Department of Information Science & Engineering has placed 80-85% of qualifying students in reputable industries, demonstrating a good track record of placement. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Overview"
  },
  {
    "question": "When did the Department of Information Science & Engineering collaborate with ICT Academy?",
    "answer": "The Department of Information Science & Engineering collaborated with ICT Academy in 2019. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Overview"
  },
  {
    "question": "What industry-based courses does the Department of Information Science & Engineering offer in collaboration with ICT Academy?",
    "answer": "The Department of Information Science & Engineering offers Google (for Cloud and Android courses), and UiPath (for Robotic Process Automation course) in collaboration with ICT Academy. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Overview"
  },
  {
    "question": "When did the Department of Information Science & Engineering become part of Google’s Career Readiness Program?",
    "answer": "The Department of Information Science & Engineering became part of Google’s Career Readiness Program in 2020. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Overview"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the placement rate of the Department of Information Science & Engineering?",
    "answer": "The Department of Information Science & Engineering has a high placement rate. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Overview"
  },
  {
    "question": "What packages do students get in the Department of Information Science & Engineering?",
    "answer": "Students in the Department of Information Science & Engineering get attractive packages. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Overview"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the high-end NVIDIA server used for in the Department of Information Science & Engineering?",
    "answer": "The high-end NVIDIA server is used to explore more into data analytics in the Department of Information Science & Engineering. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Overview"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many students does the Department of Information Science & Engineering place in reputable industries?",
    "answer": "The Department of Information Science & Engineering places 80-85% of qualifying students in reputable industries. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Overview"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the role of the Department of Information Science & Engineering in the software industry?",
    "answer": "The Department of Information Science & Engineering was founded to accommodate the needs of the software industry. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Overview"
  },
  {
    "question": "When was the intake of students in the Department of Information Science & Engineering increased to 60?",
    "answer": "The intake of students in the Department of Information Science & Engineering was increased to 60 in the year 2000. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Overview"
  },
  {
    "question": "When was the intake of students in the Department of Information Science & Engineering increased to 120?",
    "answer": "The intake of students in the Department of Information Science & Engineering was increased to 120 in the year 2016. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Overview"
  },
  {
    "question": "When was the intake of students in the Department of Information Science & Engineering increased to 180?",
    "answer": "The intake of students in the Department of Information Science & Engineering was increased to 180 in the year 2019. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Overview"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the aim of the Department of Information Science & Engineering in terms of facilities?",
    "answer": "The aim of the Department of Information Science & Engineering in terms of facilities is to provide a conducive environment for learning, research, and hands-on exploration in the dynamic field of computer science. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Overview"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the aim of the Department of Information Science & Engineering in terms of learning environment?",
    "answer": "The aim of the Department of Information Science & Engineering in terms of learning environment is to nurture curiosity, foster innovation, and prepare students for successful careers in the ever-evolving field of computer science. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Overview"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the role of the Department of Information Science & Engineering in bridging the gap between academic learning and industry demands?",
    "answer": "The Department of Information Science & Engineering maintains strong connections with industries and facilitates internship opportunities for students to bridge the gap between academic learning and industry demands. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Overview"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the role of the Department of Information Science & Engineering in terms of innovation?",
    "answer": "The Department of Information Science & Engineering provides state-of-the-art facilities where innovation meets education. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Overview"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the role of the Department of Information Science & Engineering in terms of education?",
    "answer": "The Department of Information Science & Engineering provides a conducive environment for learning, research, and hands-on exploration in the dynamic field of computer science. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Overview"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the role of the Department of Information Science & Engineering in terms of research?",
    "answer": "The Department of Information Science & Engineering provides state-of-the-art facilities for research in the dynamic field of computer science. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Overview"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the role of the Department of Information Science & Engineering in terms of hands-on exploration?",
    "answer": "The Department of Information Science & Engineering provides state-of-the-art facilities for hands-on exploration in the dynamic field of computer science. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Overview"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the role of the Department of Information Science & Engineering in terms of cultivating a learning environment?",
    "answer": "The Department of Information Science & Engineering aims to cultivate a learning environment that nurtures curiosity, fosters innovation, and prepares students for successful careers in the ever-evolving field of computer science. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Overview"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the role of the Department of Information Science & Engineering in terms of preparing students for successful careers?",
    "answer": "The Department of Information Science & Engineering aims to prepare students for successful careers in the ever-evolving field of computer science by providing a comprehensive understanding of the principles, theories, and practical applications that form the foundation of Information Science. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Overview"
  },
    {
      "question": "What is the vision of the Department of Information Science & Engineering?",
      "answer": "The vision of the Department of Information Science & Engineering is to achieve excellence in information science and engineering through a strong research and teaching environment that addresses the emerging global challenges and market demands. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Vision"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the mission of the Department of Information Science & Engineering?",
      "answer": "The mission of the Department of Information Science & Engineering is to provide outstanding education and research training to the students for their productive careers in industry, academia and government, promote active learning, critical thinking, and engineering judgment coupled with business and entrepreneurial skills, and prepare the students to practice their professions competently to meet the ever-changing needs of society and to continue learning their discipline, allowing them to move into other related fields. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Mission"
    },
    {
      "question": "How does the Department of Information Science & Engineering aim to achieve excellence in information science and engineering?",
      "answer": "The Department of Information Science & Engineering aims to achieve excellence in information science and engineering through a strong research and teaching environment that addresses the emerging global challenges and market demands. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Vision"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the commitment of the Department of Information Science & Engineering towards education and research training?",
      "answer": "The Department of Information Science & Engineering is committed to providing outstanding education and research training to the students for their productive careers in industry, academia and government. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Mission"
    },
    {
      "question": "How does the Department of Information Science & Engineering promote excellence and innovation?",
      "answer": "The Department of Information Science & Engineering promotes excellence and innovation by providing a learning environment that encourages students to achieve their full potential. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Excellence"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the focus of the Department of Information Science & Engineering in terms of ethical practice and responsibility towards society?",
      "answer": "The Department of Information Science & Engineering focuses on promoting ethical practice and responsibility towards society among its students. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#EthicalPractice"
    },
    {
      "question": "How does the Department of Information Science & Engineering prepare students for their professions?",
      "answer": "The Department of Information Science & Engineering prepares students to practice their professions competently to meet the ever-changing needs of society and to continue learning their discipline, allowing them to move into other related fields. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Preparation"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the emphasis of the Department of Information Science & Engineering in terms of active learning?",
      "answer": "The Department of Information Science & Engineering emphasizes active learning, critical thinking, and engineering judgment coupled with business and entrepreneurial skills. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#ActiveLearning"
    },
    {
      "question": "How does the Department of Information Science & Engineering promote business and entrepreneurial skills?",
      "answer": "The Department of Information Science & Engineering promotes business and entrepreneurial skills by integrating them into the curriculum and encouraging students to think creatively and innovatively. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Entrepreneurship"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the role of the Department of Information Science & Engineering in promoting ethical practice?",
      "answer": "The Department of Information Science & Engineering promotes ethical practice by incorporating ethical considerations into the curriculum and encouraging students to act responsibly and ethically in their professional and personal lives. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#EthicalPractice"
    },
    {
      "question": "How does the Department of Information Science & Engineering prepare students for the ever-changing needs of society?",
      "answer": "The Department of Information Science & Engineering prepares students to meet the ever-changing needs of society by providing a learning environment that promotes flexibility, adaptability, and lifelong learning. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#SocietyNeeds"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the focus of the Department of Information Science & Engineering in terms of research?",
      "answer": "The Department of Information Science & Engineering focuses on conducting high-quality research that addresses the emerging global challenges and market demands. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Research"
    },
    {
      "question": "How does the Department of Information Science & Engineering promote innovation?",
      "answer": "The Department of Information Science & Engineering promotes innovation by encouraging students to think creatively and providing them with the tools and resources to turn their ideas into reality. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Innovation"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the commitment of the Department of Information Science & Engineering towards excellence?",
      "answer": "The Department of Information Science & Engineering is committed to promoting excellence in all its activities, including teaching, research, and service. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Excellence"
    },
    {
      "question": "How does the Department of Information Science & Engineering foster responsibility towards society?",
      "answer": "The Department of Information Science & Engineering fosters responsibility towards society by encouraging students to engage in community service and to consider the social implications of their work. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Responsibility"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the emphasis of the Department of Information Science & Engineering in terms of critical thinking?",
      "answer": "The Department of Information Science & Engineering emphasizes critical thinking by encouraging students to analyze complex problems and to develop creative solutions. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#CriticalThinking"
    },
    {
      "question": "How does the Department of Information Science & Engineering promote engineering judgment?",
      "answer": "The Department of Information Science & Engineering promotes engineering judgment by providing students with practical experience and opportunities to apply their knowledge to real-world problems. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#EngineeringJudgment"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the role of the Department of Information Science & Engineering in promoting entrepreneurship?",
      "answer": "The Department of Information Science & Engineering promotes entrepreneurship by encouraging students to think creatively and to develop their business and leadership skills. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Entrepreneurship"
    },
    {
      "question": "How does the Department of Information Science & Engineering promote ethical practice and responsibility towards society?",
      "answer": "The Department of Information Science & Engineering promotes ethical practice and responsibility towards society by incorporating ethical considerations into the curriculum and encouraging students to act responsibly and ethically in their professional and personal lives. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#EthicalPractice"
    },
    {
      "question": "How does the Department of Information Science & Engineering prepare students for the future?",
      "answer": "The Department of Information Science & Engineering prepares students for the future by providing them with the knowledge, skills, and attitudes necessary to succeed in a rapidly changing world. For further details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#Future"
    },
    {
      "question": "what is the syllabus of Information Science & Engineering department for the batch 2022-2026?",
      "answer": "the syllabus of Information Science & Engineering department for the batch 2022-2026 is avaliable at the college website, For more details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/syllabus/ndu/2022-26/B.Tech._IS_Regulations_2022.pdf"
    },
    {
      "question": "what is the syllabus of Information Science & Engineering department for the batch 2023-2027?",
      "answer": "the syllabus of Information Science & Engineering department for the batch 2022-2026 is avaliable at the college website, For more details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/syllabus/ndu/2022-26/B.Tech._IS_Regulations_2023.pdf"
    },
    {
      "question": "what is the syllabus of Information Science & Engineering department for the minor degree?",
      "answer": "the syllabus of Information Science & Engineering department for the batch 2022-2026 is avaliable at the college website, For more details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/syllabus/ndu/MinorDegree/MinorDegree-DataScience.pdf"
    },
    {
      "question": "what is the syllabus of Information Science & Engineering department for the batch VTU third year?",
      "answer": "the syllabus of Information Science & Engineering department for the batch 2022-2026 is avaliable at the college website, For more details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/syllabus/ifs/V-VI-ISE.pdf"
    },
    {
      "question": "what is the syllabus of Information Science & Engineering department for the batch VTU fourth year?",
      "answer": "the syllabus of Information Science & Engineering department for the batch 2022-2026 is avaliable at the college website, For more details please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/syllabus/ifs/VII&VIII-ISE.pdf"
    },
    {
        "question": "what are the list of MoU signed?",
        "answer": "the list of MoU is a listed on college website, For further details Please visit https://nmamit.nitte.edu.in/department-information-science.php#MoU"
    }
    {
        "question": "What are Dr. ASHWINI B's educational qualifications?",
        "answer": "Dr. ASHWINI B holds a Ph.D. from VTU Belagavi in 2019, an M.Tech in Computer Science from VTU (Autonomous) in 2011, and a B.E. in Information Science and Engineering from VTU in 2004."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are Dr. ASHWINI B's areas of interest?",
        "answer": "Dr. ASHWINI B's areas of interest include Image Processing, Computer Vision, and Machine Learning."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are Dr. ASHWINI B's departmental responsibilities?",
        "answer": "Dr. ASHWINI B serves as the Head of the Department from August 2023 onwards, a Team Member of Project Vriddhi by Nitte University, UG coordinator for 5 years, Department placement Coordinator until August 2023, and Vista Coordinator for 2 years."
    },
    {
        "question": "What professional memberships does Dr. ASHWINI B have?",
        "answer": "Dr. ASHWINI B is a member of IEEE, WIE, and serves as an Executive Committee member of the IEEE Mangalore Subsection."
    },
    {
        "question": "What subjects has Dr. ASHWINI B handled?",
        "answer": "Dr. ASHWINI B has handled subjects such as Java Programming, Mobile application Development using Android, Algorithms, Operating System, Business Intelligence, Data Mining, Software Engineering, and Machine Learning."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are Dr. BALASUBRAMANI R's educational qualifications?",
        "answer": "Dr. BALASUBRAMANI R holds a Ph.D. in Information Technology from Vinayaka Missions Research Foundation (Deemed-to-be-University), Salem in 2011, an M.Tech in Information Technology from Allahabad Agricultural Institute (Deemed-to-be-University), Allahabad in 2005, and a B.E. in Electronics and Communication Engineering from Madurai Kamaraj University, Madurai in 1990."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. BALASUBRAMANI R's past experience?",
        "answer": "Dr. BALASUBRAMANI R has extensive experience including roles such as Professor of ISE, Facility Incharge, Chief Project Leader of EDC & STEP, Executive Head of MSME Business Incubation Centre, Head of the Department of ISE, Associate Professor of ISE, Assistant Professor of CSE, and Assistant Professor of IT at various institutions. Additionally, he has worked as an Intern at EmconEmsys Technologies Pvt. Ltd., Chennai, Senior Faculty at Microtech Computers, Pudukkottai, and Service Engineer at Puresine Electronics, Bangalore."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are Dr. BALASUBRAMANI R's areas of interest?",
        "answer": "Dr. BALASUBRAMANI R's areas of interest include Artificial Intelligence, Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Image Processing, Data Science, Data Mining, Digital Transformation, Digital Marketing, Digital Entrepreneurship, and Education Technology (Outcome Based Education)."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are Dr. BALASUBRAMANI R's departmental responsibilities?",
        "answer": "Dr. BALASUBRAMANI R serves as a Professor in the Dept. of Information Science & Engineering, Facility Incharge of Nitte Startup Ecospace Institute, NBA (National Board of Accreditation) Coordinator, Faculty Sponsor of ACM Student Chapter, Faculty Incharge of Development Students Club (DSC) supported by Google Developers, and Faculty Incharge of Salesforce Students Community. Additionally, he is a Faculty SPoC of ICT Academy, UiPath Academic Alliance Campus Advisor, Educator for Google for Education, Google Cloud, and UiPath, Coordinator for Faculty SIG on Data Science & Big Data Analytics (DS & BDA), Social Media Coordinator of NMAMIT Institute Innovation Council (IIC), and member of various boards and committees within the Information Science and Engineering Department."
    },
    {
        "question": "What professional memberships does Dr. BALASUBRAMANI R have?",
        "answer": "Dr. BALASUBRAMANI R is a member of International Association of Engineers (IAENG), Indian Society for Technical Education (ISTE), Association for Computing Machinery (ACM), Chartered Management Institute (CMI), Institute for Engineering Research and Publications (IFERP), Institute of Data Science and Artificial Intelligence (IDSAI), and is a Certified IonCUDOS Subject Matter Expert for Outcome Based Education."
    },
    {
        "question": "What subjects has Dr. BALASUBRAMANI R handled?",
        "answer": "Dr. BALASUBRAMANI R has handled subjects such as Robotic Process Automation Design & Development (UiPath Studio), Architecting with Google Compute Engine (Google Cloud), Data Mining, Software Engineering, Object Oriented Analysis & Design with UML, Computer Networks, Computer Organization and Architecture, OOPS using C++, Java Programming & Web Technology, Programming and Data Structures using C, TCP/IP Design & Implementation, Digital Image Processing, Advanced DBMS, Advanced Java Programming, Essentials of Information Technology, Business Intelligence & its Applications, Building Enterprise Applications, Computer Graphics and Visualization."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are Dr. KARUNA PANDIT's educational qualifications?",
        "answer": "Dr. KARUNA PANDIT holds a Ph.D. from NITK, Surathkal in 2014, an M.Tech from NITK, Surathkal in 1999, and an M.Sc from Mangalore University in 1984."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. KARUNA PANDIT's past experience?",
        "answer": "Dr. KARUNA PANDIT has served in various positions at NMAM Institute of Technology from Lecturer to Professor, including roles such as Lecturer, Senior Lecturer, Assistant Professor, Associate Professor, and HOD. Their tenure spans from September 1987 to the present."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are Dr. KARUNA PANDIT's areas of interest?",
        "answer": "Dr. KARUNA PANDIT's areas of interest include Cryptography and Random number Generation."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are Dr. KARUNA PANDIT's departmental responsibilities?",
        "answer": "Dr. KARUNA PANDIT serves as the NAAC Coordinator."
    },
    {
        "question": "What professional memberships does Dr. KARUNA PANDIT have?",
        "answer": "Dr. KARUNA PANDIT is a Life Member of Indian Society for Technical Education, Life Member of Indian Society of Systems for Science And Engineering, and a Life member of Cryptology Research Society of India."
    },
    {
        "question": "What subjects has Dr. KARUNA PANDIT handled?",
        "answer": "Dr. KARUNA PANDIT has handled subjects such as Probability, Statistics and Queuing, Discrete Mathematical Structure, Operation Research, C programming, Object oriented Programming with C++, Operating Systems, Design and Analysis of Algorithms, System Simulation and Modelling, Cryptography, and Network Security."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are Dr. KARTHIK PAI B. H.'s educational qualifications?",
        "answer": "Dr. KARTHIK PAI B. H. holds a Ph.D. in Computer Science & Engineering from VTU, Belgaum in 2018, an M. Tech. in Computer Science & Engineering from VTU, Belgaum in 2003, and a B.E. in Computer Science & Engineering from Karnatak University, Dharwad in 1998."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. KARTHIK PAI B. H.'s past experience?",
        "answer": "Dr. KARTHIK PAI B. H. has served as a Lecturer in the Dept. of CSE at KVG College of Engineering, Sullia from 14/06/1999 to 17/09/1999, a Lecturer in the Dept. of CSE at TMAPP, Manipal from 20/09/1999 to 30/09/2000, and as an Assistant Professor/Associate Professor in the Dept. of ISE at NMAMIT from 2000 to 2017. They have been serving as a Professor in the Dept. of ISE at NMAMIT since 2018."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are Dr. KARTHIK PAI B. H.'s areas of interest?",
        "answer": "Dr. KARTHIK PAI B. H.'s areas of interest include Software Engineering, Computer Networks, Advanced Computer Architecture, and Networks and Security."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are Dr. KARTHIK PAI B. H.'s departmental responsibilities?",
        "answer": "Dr. KARTHIK PAI B. H. serves as the Internal ISO Coordinator."
    },
    {
        "question": "What professional memberships does Dr. KARTHIK PAI B. H. have?",
        "answer": "Dr. KARTHIK PAI B. H. is a Member of the Indian Society for Technical Education."
    },
    {
        "question": "What subjects has Dr. KARTHIK PAI B. H. handled?",
        "answer": "Dr. KARTHIK PAI B. H. has handled subjects such as Advanced Computer Architecture, Software Engineering, Cloud Infrastructure & Services, Computer Networks, Design Thinking, Intrusion Detection Systems, Supply Chain Management and ERP, Internet of Things, Data Communication, Computer Organization and Architecture, Unix & Shell Programming, Operating Systems, Fundamentals of Cyber Security, and Industrial Engineering Management."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Dr. RAVI B's highest educational qualification?",
        "answer": "Ph.D in Computer Science Engineering from REVA University, Bangalore, India"
      },
      {
        "question": "Where did Dr. RAVI B obtain their M.Tech degree?",
        "answer": "Sri Jayachamarajendra College Of Engineering, Mysore"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which institution awarded Dr. RAVI B their B.E degree?",
        "answer": "NMAM Institute of Technology, Nitte, Udupi"
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Dr. RAVI B's primary areas of interest?",
        "answer": "Graph Algorithms, Wireless sensor network, Internet of Things, Database, Theoretical Computer Science"
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Dr. USHA DIVAKARLA's educational qualifications?",
        "answer": "B.E (2000) in Computer Science and Engineering (CSE) from Bangalore University, Kalpataru Institute of Technology, Tiptur. M.Tech (2006) in Computer Science and Engineering (CSE) from Maharshi Dayanand University, Haryana, YMCA Engineering College, Faridabad. Ph.D (2018) in Trust Management in Cloud Computing from NITK Surathkal."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where has Dr. USHA DIVAKARLA worked in the past?",
        "answer": "Dr. USHA DIVAKARLA has worked at St Joseph Engineering College, Vamajoor, Mangalore, Karnataka, India from July 2018 to Dec 2020. Canara Engineering College, Benjanapadavu, Mangalore, Karnataka, India from Feb 2017 to June 2018. PES Institute of Technology and Management, Shimoga, India from July 2011 to Dec 2011. BITS-Pilani and Hyderabad Campus, Hyderabad, India from April 2008 to June 2011. Lingaya Institute of Technology and Management, Faridabad, India from July 2006 to Mar 2008."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Dr. USHA DIVAKARLA's areas of interest?",
        "answer": "Dr. USHA DIVAKARLA's areas of interest include Cloud Computing, Trust Management, Autonomous Computing, and Machine Learning."
      },
      {
        "question": "What achievement has Dr. USHA DIVAKARLA received?",
        "answer": "Dr. USHA DIVAKARLA received the Best Paper Award for the paper 'Load Balancing of Virtual Machine Resources in Cloud Using Genetic Algorithm', presented at the International Conference on Communication Networks (ICCN 2013)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Dr. USHA DIVAKARLA's departmental responsibilities?",
        "answer": "Dr. USHA DIVAKARLA's departmental responsibilities include being the IEEE Coordinator, Data Science/IoT Theme Incharge, and Coursera Coordinator."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which subjects has Dr. USHA DIVAKARLA handled?",
        "answer": "Dr. USHA DIVAKARLA has handled subjects such as Advanced Computer Architecture, Internet of Things, Artificial Intelligence, Microcontrollers and Embedded Systems, Software Engineering, Machine Learning, Software Project Management, Software Architecture, and Object Oriented Analysis and Design."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Dr. MANJULA GURURAJ RAO's educational qualifications?",
        "answer": "Dr. MANJULA GURURAJ RAO holds a Ph.D. in Computer Science & Engineering from Jain University (2020), an M.Tech in Computer Science & Engineering from AAIDU Naini Allahabad, affiliated to Allahabad Agricultural Deemed University (2006), and a B.E in Computer Science & Engineering from NMAMIT Nitte, Mangalore University (2001)."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where has Dr. MANJULA GURURAJ RAO worked in the past?",
        "answer": "Dr. MANJULA GURURAJ RAO has worked as an Associate Professor in the Dept. of ISE at NMAMIT Nitte since August 2021. They have also served as Guest Faculty at DayanadaSagar University for M.Tech classes (academic year 2017-2018), HOD & Associate Professor at NITMS (July 2010 to July 2017), Sr. Lecturer at K.S.I.T, Bangalore (Sept 2004 to June 2010), Lecturer at DSCE Bangalore (Sept 2002 to Sep 2004), and Lecturer at KVGCE, Sullia (Dec 2001 to June 2002)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Dr. MANJULA GURURAJ RAO's departmental responsibilities?",
        "answer": "Dr. MANJULA GURURAJ RAO's departmental responsibilities include being the NACC- Criteria 3 Coordinator and Research Coordinator."
      },
      {
        "question": "What professional memberships does Dr. MANJULA GURURAJ RAO hold?",
        "answer": "Dr. MANJULA GURURAJ RAO is a member of IEEE and ISTE."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which subjects has Dr. MANJULA GURURAJ RAO handled?",
        "answer": "Dr. MANJULA GURURAJ RAO has handled subjects such as Computer Concepts & C Programming (Theory + Lab), Design and Analysis of Algorithms (Theory + Lab), Java & J2EE (Theory + Lab), Data Structures with C (Theory + Lab), OOPS with C++ (Theory + Lab), Data mining and Data Warehouse, Advances in Operating Systems, Microprocessors (Theory + Lab), Computer Organization, Distributed Systems, Systems Programming (Theory + Lab), Computer Graphics (Theory + Lab), Advanced Algorithms, Natural Language Processing, Machine Learning, C Programming, Distributed Computing, OOMD, Unix and Shell Programing, Object Oriented and C++, and Data Communications."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Dr. SUMATHI PAWAR's educational qualifications?",
        "answer": "Dr. SUMATHI PAWAR holds a Ph.D. in Computer/Information Systems (September 2017) from VTU and an M.Tech. in System Analysis and Computer Application (May 2009) from NITK."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where has Dr. SUMATHI PAWAR worked in the past?",
        "answer": "Dr. SUMATHI PAWAR joined as Associate Professor in NMAMIT, Nitte, Karkala on 02-08-2021. They also worked as a lecturer in the CSE department of Canara Engineering College, BenjanaPadavu, Bantwal starting from August 2004. They were promoted to Senior Lecturer in August 2006, Assistant Professor grade-3 in August 2010, and Associate Professor in November 2012. Additionally, they were deputed as HOD of Information Science Engineering from December 2017."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Dr. SUMATHI PAWAR's areas of interest?",
        "answer": "Dr. SUMATHI PAWAR's areas of interest include Web Services, Cloud Computing, Data Mining, Machine Learning, and Computer Networks."
      },
      {
        "question": "What achievements has Dr. SUMATHI PAWAR accomplished?",
        "answer": "Dr. SUMATHI PAWAR has published 8 international indexed papers in one year and applied for funds of Government Research agencies which include DST, DBT, and VGST in the year 2023. They received a fund from AICTE towards MODROBS project titled 'ADVANCED NETWORKS AND DISTRIBUTED PROCESSING LABORATORY' and successfully finished the project. Dr. SUMATHI PAWAR was recognized as a SILVER partner faculty under Inspire - The Campus Connect Faculty Partnership Model -2015, 2016 & 2017 of Infosys Campus Connect. They also received a Best Paper Award in National Level Paper presentation Anveeksha-09 and qualified GATE-2012 with a percentile of 83.2% in OBC(Non-creamy category)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Dr. SUMATHI PAWAR's departmental responsibilities?",
        "answer": "Dr. SUMATHI PAWAR's departmental responsibilities include being the Infosys Spoc, UGC-Co-Coordinator, NAAC Co-Coordinator, PG Coordinator, Project Coordinator, Research Coordinator, Attendance Coordinator, Technical Coordinator, Discipline Coordinator, Test Coordinator and Maintenance Coordinator, Student-Performance Cell Coordinator, and Criteria 7 Coordinator."
      },
      {
        "question": "What professional memberships does Dr. SUMATHI PAWAR hold?",
        "answer": "Dr. SUMATHI PAWAR is a member of MISTE and ISTE."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which subjects has Dr. SUMATHI PAWAR handled?",
        "answer": "Dr. SUMATHI PAWAR has handled subjects such as Web 2.0 and Rich Internet Applications, Object Oriented Programming Using Java and C++, Computer Organization and Architecture, Software Engineering, Machine Learning Lab, Python Programming, Service Oriented Architecture, Protocol Engineering, Internet of Things, System Programming, System Software, Operating System, Mobile Application Development, Data Mining, Computer Networks, Advanced DataBase Management, File Structures, Web Services, Service Oriented Architecture, Computer Organization, DBMS, Advanced DBMS, C Programming, C++ Programming, Java Programming, OOC File structures, Cloud computing, Distributed Operating Systems, .NET Programming, and Web development."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Dr. NAGANNA CHETTY's educational qualifications?",
        "answer": "Dr. NAGANNA CHETTY holds a Ph.D. in Information Systems from NITK, Surathkal in 2022, an M. Tech. in Computer Science & Engineering from VTU, Belgaum in 2006, and a B.E. in Computer Science & Engineering from Gulbarga University, Gulbarga in 1999."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where has Dr. NAGANNA CHETTY worked in the past?",
        "answer": "Dr. NAGANNA CHETTY has worked in various academic institutions and roles, including Lecturer positions in NES Polytechnic Gulbarga, MBES’s College of Engineering, Ambajogai, and BLDEA’s College of Engineering. They also served as Assistant Professor in Graphic Era Institute of Technology, Quantum School of Technology, Galgotias University, and Mangalore Institute of Technology and Engineering. Additionally, they worked as temporary faculty at the National Institute of Technology Karnataka Surathkal and as a Professor in the Department of Information Science and Engineering at A. J. Institute of Engineering and Technology, Mangaluru."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Dr. NAGANNA CHETTY's areas of interest?",
        "answer": "Dr. NAGANNA CHETTY's areas of interest include Data Mining, Data Science, Social Media Content Analysis, Digital Governance, and Machine Learning."
      },
      {
        "question": "What departmental responsibilities does Dr. NAGANNA CHETTY have?",
        "answer": "Dr. NAGANNA CHETTY serves as a Project Coordinator."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which subjects has Dr. NAGANNA CHETTY handled?",
        "answer": "Dr. NAGANNA CHETTY has handled subjects such as Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning, DataWarehouse and DataMining, Computer Networks, Database Management System, Distributed System, Advanced Database Management System, Operating System, Internet of Things, and Operating Systems."
      },
      {
        "question": "How many BE and M.Tech. projects has Dr. NAGANNA CHETTY guided?",
        "answer": "Dr. NAGANNA CHETTY has guided 15 BE projects and 3 M.Tech. projects."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Dr. JASON ELROY MARTIS's educational qualifications?",
        "answer": "Dr. JASON ELROY MARTIS holds a B.E. in Information Science and Engineering (CSE) from Visvesvaraya Technological University, Belagavi (2009), an M.Tech in Computer Science and Engineering (CSE) from Visvesvaraya Technological University, Belagavi (2013), an M.B.A in Marketing from Karnataka State Open University, Mysore (2014), and a Ph.D. from Visvesvaraya Technological University, Belagavi (2021) with a thesis entitled 'A Deterministic Approach for Mood Estimation using Real Time Data'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Dr. JASON ELROY MARTIS's areas of interest?",
        "answer": "Dr. JASON ELROY MARTIS's areas of interest include Deep Learning, Artificial Intelligence, Internet of Things, Machine Learning, Computer Vision, Cyber Security, Human Computer Interaction, Image Processing, Cognitive AI, Generative AI, Internet of Things, and Cryptography."
      },
      {
        "question": "What achievements has Dr. JASON ELROY MARTIS accomplished?",
        "answer": "Dr. JASON ELROY MARTIS was nominated for the 'Young Scientist Award' under the International Research and Academic Excellence Awards 2021 held by the 9th International Online Conference on Recent Innovative Research. They were also identified as a Technical Program Committee member for the 2020 Second International Conference on Soft Computing and its Engineering Applications. Additionally, Dr. JASON ELROY MARTIS received appreciation for the in-house development of a Smart Classroom device installed at LH500 classroom 5th Floor APJ Block NMAMIT, and received KCST Funding for creating a framework for the 'Automatic Classification of Bacterial Clusters using Transfer Learning' which is currently deployed in-house in their Deep Learning Server at NMAMIT. They also won 9th Place in WHO Product Development for Vaccines Advisory Competition 2019 for assisting in the development of a cost-effective IoT sensor in Vaccine Logistics Management."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Dr. JASON ELROY MARTIS's departmental responsibilities?",
        "answer": "Dr. JASON ELROY MARTIS's departmental responsibilities include being the IoT Branch level Coordinator, Startup/Consultancy Coordinator, Infrastructure Coordinator, In-house projects Coordinator, MoU Coordinator, and NVIDIA Coordinator."
      },
      {
        "question": "What professional memberships does Dr. JASON ELROY MARTIS hold?",
        "answer": "Dr. JASON ELROY MARTIS is a member of the Indian Society for Technical Education (ISTE), New Delhi, India."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which subjects has Dr. JASON ELROY MARTIS handled?",
        "answer": "Dr. JASON ELROY MARTIS has handled subjects such as Database Management Systems, Internet of Things, Artificial Intelligence, Microcontrollers and Embedded Systems, Machine Learning, Object Oriented Analysis and Design, Computer Organization, Database Management Systems, Image Processing, Operations Research, Operating Systems, Computer organization and Architecture, Information and Network Security, Java Programming, Advanced Java Programming, Deep Learning, Generative Adversarial Networks, Internet and Web Programming, C#.NET technologies, Operations Research, Data Communications, and Object-Oriented Programming."
      },
      {
        "question": "How many BE and M.Tech projects has Dr. JASON ELROY MARTIS guided?",
        "answer": "Dr. JASON ELROY MARTIS has guided 52 B.E. projects and 3 M.Tech projects."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Dr. BOLA SUNIL KAMATH's educational qualifications?",
        "answer": "Dr. BOLA SUNIL KAMATH holds a Ph.D and an M.Tech in Computer Science and Engineering from Manipal University, obtained in 2006, and a B.E in Computer Science from Mangalore University, obtained in 2000."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where has Dr. BOLA SUNIL KAMATH worked in the past?",
        "answer": "Dr. BOLA SUNIL KAMATH has worked as a Computer Lecturer in the Department of Computer Science & Engineering at MIT Manipal from 2000 to 2006, as a Lecturer in the Department of Computer Science & Engineering at City Engineering College, Bangalore from March 2007 to October 2007, as a Lecturer in the Department of Computer Science & Engineering at RNSIT, Bangalore from February 2008 to May 2008, as an Assistant Professor in the Department of Information Science & Engineering at AMC, Bangalore from May 2008 to August 2009, as an Assistant Professor in the Department of Information Science & Engineering at AIET, Moodabidri from August 2009 to May 2010, and as an Associate Professor in the Department of Computer Science & Engineering at SJEC, Mangalore from May 2010 to July 2019."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Dr. BOLA SUNIL KAMATH's areas of interest?",
        "answer": "Dr. BOLA SUNIL KAMATH's areas of interest include Computer Networks & Network Security, Cloud Computing, Computer vision, and Machine Learning."
      },
      {
        "question": "What departmental responsibilities does Dr. BOLA SUNIL KAMATH have?",
        "answer": "Dr. BOLA SUNIL KAMATH's departmental responsibilities include being the UHV Coordinator, Internship Coordinator, and Sports Coordinator."
      },
      {
        "question": "What professional memberships does Dr. BOLA SUNIL KAMATH hold?",
        "answer": "Dr. BOLA SUNIL KAMATH is an institutional member of CSI (Computer Society of India)."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which subjects has Dr. BOLA SUNIL KAMATH handled?",
        "answer": "Dr. BOLA SUNIL KAMATH has handled subjects such as Problem solving using C & Lab, Logic Design & Lab, Datastructures & Lab, Microprocessors & Microcontroller & Lab, System Software & Lab, Automata Theory & Computability, Compiler Design & Lab, Computer Graphics, Web Programming & Lab, Cryptography & Cyber Law, Computer Networks, Cloud Computing, Finite Automata and Formal Languages, UI Design, Management and Entrepreneurship for IT Industry, Business Enterprise Design, Computer Vision, and Operating System C."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Dr. MANJUNATHA's educational qualifications?",
        "answer": "Dr. MANJUNATHA holds a Ph.D and an M.Tech in Computer Science & Engineering from NMAMIT, Nitte, obtained in 2009, and a B.E in Computer Science & Engineering from Sri Jayachamarajendra College of Engineering Mysore, obtained in 2005."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where has Dr. MANJUNATHA worked in the past?",
        "answer": "Dr. MANJUNATHA has worked as an Assistant Professor at SDM Institute of Technology, Ujire from 2009 to 2021, as a Lecturer at Moodlakatte Institute of Technology, Kundapura from 2006 to 2007, and as a Software Engineer at Surabhi Technologies, Bangalore from 2005 to 2006."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Dr. MANJUNATHA's areas of interest?",
        "answer": "Dr. MANJUNATHA's areas of interest include Big Data Analytics, Data Science, Machine Learning, and Internet of Things."
      },
      {
        "question": "What departmental responsibilities does Dr. MANJUNATHA have?",
        "answer": "Dr. MANJUNATHA's departmental responsibilities include being the NBA Co-coordinator."
      },
      {
        "question": "What professional memberships does Dr. MANJUNATHA hold?",
        "answer": "Dr. MANJUNATHA is a member of IEEE, ACM, and ISTE."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which subjects has Dr. MANJUNATHA handled?",
        "answer": "Dr. MANJUNATHA has handled subjects such as Java and J2EE, Computer Graphics and Visualization using OpenGL, Database Management Systems, Computer Networks, Analysis and Design of Algorithms, Graph Theory and Combinatorics, Discrete Mathematical Structures, Data Structures with C, and OOP with C++."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is Mr. DEVIDAS's past experience?",
        "answer": "Mr. DEVIDAS has 14 years of past experience."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Mr. DEVIDAS's areas of interest?",
        "answer": "Mr. DEVIDAS's areas of interest include Data Science/Analytics, Web/Mobile Application development, and Cloud computing."
      },
      {
        "question": "What achievements has Mr. DEVIDAS accomplished?",
        "answer": "Mr. DEVIDAS was recognized as a BRONZE Level partner faculty under Inspire - The Campus Connect Faculty Partnership Model during Inspire 2017. They received KSCST project Funding in 2011 and 2015 and won Best Project awards in Expro project Exhibition in 2012, 2015, and 2016."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Mr. DEVIDAS's departmental responsibilities?",
        "answer": "Mr. DEVIDAS's departmental responsibilities include being the Project Coordinator, Infosys Campus Connect Coordinator, Oracle Academic Alliance VISTA Coordinator, and UG Alumni Coordinator."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which subjects has Mr. DEVIDAS handled?",
        "answer": "Mr. DEVIDAS has handled subjects such as Data Mining, Business Intelligence, Mobile Application development, Java & its Applications, Object Oriented Programming, Building Enterprise Applications, Distributed Systems, and Data Structures."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Mr. VASUDEVA PAI's educational qualifications?",
        "answer": "Mr. VASUDEVA PAI is pursuing a Ph.D. He holds an M.Tech in Computer Science & Engineering from VTU, Belagavi, obtained in 2010, and a B.E. in Information Science & Engineering from JNNCE, Shivamoga, obtained in 2005."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where has Mr. VASUDEVA PAI worked in the past?",
        "answer": "Mr. VASUDEVA PAI worked as a Software Engineer in Lotus Global Technology, Bangalore from 2005 to 2006. Later, he served as a Lecturer at Moodlakatte Institute of Technology, Kundapur from 2006 to 2007. Subsequently, he held the positions of Assistant Professor Gd-I at NMAMIT, Nitte from 2007 and Assistant Professor Gd-II at NMAMIT, Nitte from 2015."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Mr. VASUDEVA PAI's areas of interest?",
        "answer": "Mr. VASUDEVA PAI's areas of interest include Wireless Networks Security, Internet Of Things, Computer Vision, and Deep Learning."
      },
      {
        "question": "What departmental responsibilities does Mr. VASUDEVA PAI have?",
        "answer": "Mr. VASUDEVA PAI's departmental responsibilities include being the VMWare IT Academy PG Coordinator, PG Alumni Coordinator, Nitte News and NMAMIT News Bulletin Coordinator, ISO Coordinator, EDC Coordinator, NAIN Mentor, ISTE Chairman, and Project Coordinator."
      },
      {
        "question": "What professional memberships does Mr. VASUDEVA PAI hold?",
        "answer": "Mr. VASUDEVA PAI is a Life Time member of the Institute of Engineers (India) and the Indian Society for Technical Education."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which subjects has Mr. VASUDEVA PAI handled?",
        "answer": "Mr. VASUDEVA PAI has handled subjects such as Compiler Design, Finite Automata and Formal Languages, Data Communication, Computer Networks, Information Security, Microprocessor and Interfacing, System Software, Object-oriented Programming with C++, Management Information System, Design Thinking, Cyber Security, Cryptography and Network Security, Advanced Computer Networks, and Digital Communication."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Ms. DEEPA's educational qualifications?",
        "answer": "Ms. DEEPA holds a B.E obtained in 2005, an M.Tech obtained in 2012, and is currently pursuing a Ph.D."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Ms. DEEPA's areas of interest?",
        "answer": "Ms. DEEPA's areas of interest include Image Processing and Computer Vision."
      },
      {
        "question": "What departmental responsibilities does Ms. DEEPA have?",
        "answer": "Ms. DEEPA's departmental responsibilities include being the NAAC Coordinator and UG Coordinator."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which subjects has Ms. DEEPA handled?",
        "answer": "Ms. DEEPA has handled subjects such as Data Structures, Discrete Mathematical structures, Data Mining, Design and Analysis of Algorithms, Software Engineering, Operating Systems, Object-Oriented Modeling and Design, Graph Theory, Unix and shell programming, Systems simulation and Modeling, Python Programming, and Big Data & Analytics."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Ms. RASHMI NAVEEN's educational qualifications?",
        "answer": "Ms. RASHMI NAVEEN is pursuing a Ph.D. She holds an M.Tech in Computer Science from NMAM Institute of Technology, Nitte, VTU, Karnataka (2010-2012), and a B.E. in Computer Science from TKIET, Warananagar, Shivaji University, Maharashtra (2001-2005)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is Ms. RASHMI NAVEEN's past experience?",
        "answer": "Ms. RASHMI NAVEEN has been working as an Assistant Professor-II in the Department of Information Science & Engineering at NMAMIT, Nitte since February 2007."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Ms. RASHMI NAVEEN's areas of interest?",
        "answer": "Ms. RASHMI NAVEEN's areas of interest include Information Security, Cryptography, and Steganography."
      },
      {
        "question": "What departmental responsibilities does Ms. RASHMI NAVEEN have?",
        "answer": "Ms. RASHMI NAVEEN's departmental responsibilities include being the VISTA Co-Coordinator, QS-IGUAGE Coordinator, and IQAC Coordinator."
      },
      {
        "question": "What professional memberships does Ms. RASHMI NAVEEN hold?",
        "answer": "Ms. RASHMI NAVEEN is a Life Member of the Indian Society for Technical Education."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which subjects has Ms. RASHMI NAVEEN handled?",
        "answer": "Ms. RASHMI NAVEEN has handled subjects such as Computer Organization & Architecture, Digital Systems Design, Object Oriented Programming, Unix & Shell Programming, Distributed Systems & Objects, Java & Internet Technology, Cloud Computing, and Management Information System."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Mr. ABHISHEK S RAO's educational qualifications?",
        "answer": "Mr. ABHISHEK S RAO is currently pursuing a Ph.D. at Visvesvaraya Technological University, Belagavi. He holds an M.Tech in Computer Science from NMAM Institute of Technology, Nitte, Visvesvaraya Technological University, Belagavi (2012), an M.B.A in Operations Management from Assam down town University (2014), and a B.E. in Information Science & Engineering from Canara Engineering College, Mangaluru, Visvesvaraya Technological University, Belagavi (2008)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is Mr. ABHISHEK S RAO's past experience?",
        "answer": "Mr. ABHISHEK S RAO has worked as a Software Engineer at Lasersoft Infosystems Ltd., Mangaluru (01/07/2008 to 17/03/2010), a Lecturer in the Dept. of CSE at Canara Engineering College (04/06/2012 to 30/06/2012), an Assistant Professor Gd-I in the Dept. of CSE at Canara Engineering College (04/06/2012 to 30/06/2017), and an Assistant Professor Gd-II in the Dept. of ISE at NMAM Institute of Technology (01/07/2017 to 30/06/2022)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Mr. ABHISHEK S RAO's areas of interest?",
        "answer": "Mr. ABHISHEK S RAO's areas of interest include Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Computer Vision, and Operations Research."
      },
      {
        "question": "What achievement has Mr. ABHISHEK S RAO received?",
        "answer": "The project titled 'Identification and Detection of Unusual Events in Surveillance Video Scenes Using Deep Learning Approach' has achieved significant recognition and support. It has been chosen for funding by KSCST, Govt. of Karnataka, and has been honored with the prestigious Best Project of the Year award in the Information Science Engineering department for 2023 at ExPro 2023, NMAMIT, Nitte."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Mr. ABHISHEK S RAO's departmental responsibilities?",
        "answer": "Mr. ABHISHEK S RAO's departmental responsibilities include being the VISTA Coordinator, Project Coordinator, Member of DAAB, YRC Coordinator, Class Mentor for Third Year, Dept. Coordinator for Indian Society for Technical Education (ISTE) from 1st July 2017, UGC Co-Coordinator from 1 March 2022, Interdisciplinary Projects Coordinator from 1st March 2022, EDC Co-Coordinator from 1 March 2022, and Coordinator for Indian Society for Technical Education (ISTE) from 1st July 2017 to 30-06-2023. He also serves as the MoU Coordinator from August 1st 2023."
      },
      {
        "question": "What professional memberships does Mr. ABHISHEK S RAO hold?",
        "answer": "Mr. ABHISHEK S RAO is a Member of the Indian Society for Technical Education and the International Association of Engineers."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which subjects has Mr. ABHISHEK S RAO handled?",
        "answer": "Mr. ABHISHEK S RAO has handled subjects such as Deep Learning, Innovative Management and Business Models, Machine Learning, Data Warehousing & Data Mining, Java Programming, C Programming, Web Technology, Microcontroller & Embedded Systems, Microprocessor & Interfacing, Database Management System, Advances in Database Management System, Computer Graphics & Visualization, Operations Research, Supply Chain Management, Management Information System, and Information Security Management, among others."
      },
      {
        "question": "What conferences/CME/workshops has Mr. ABHISHEK S RAO participated in?",
        "answer": "Mr. ABHISHEK S RAO has participated in numerous workshops and programs including those on Data Science, Machine Learning, Research Grants, Publications, Consultancy Skills, Image Processing, Artificial Intelligence, Deep Learning, Natural Language Processing, and more."
      },
      {
        "question": "How many B.E. projects has Mr. ABHISHEK S RAO guided?",
        "answer": "Mr. ABHISHEK S RAO has guided 22 B.E. projects."
      },
      {
        "question": "What additional information is available about Mr. ABHISHEK S RAO?",
        "answer": "Mr. ABHISHEK S RAO is a Visiting Faculty at Justice K S Hegde Institute of Management, NMAM Institute of Technology, Nitte. He has received funding from Vision Group on Science & Technology (VGST), Govt. of Karnataka for various projects."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Ms. CHINMAI SHETTY's educational qualifications?",
        "answer": "Ms. CHINMAI SHETTY is currently pursuing a Ph.D. She holds an M.Tech in Computer Science And Engineering from VTU in 2013 and a B.E. in Computer Science And Engineering from VTU in 2009."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is Ms. CHINMAI SHETTY's past experience?",
        "answer": "Ms. CHINMAI SHETTY has served as an Assistant Lecturer at the Department Of IT, NITK Surathkal (July 2009 to February 2010), an Assistant Professor at the Department OF CSE, AIET, Moodabidri (March 2010 to July 2015), and currently holds the position of Assistant Professor Gd-II at the Dept Of ISE, NMAMIT Nitte."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Ms. CHINMAI SHETTY's areas of interest?",
        "answer": "Ms. CHINMAI SHETTY's areas of interest include Machine Learning, Cloud Computing, Networks, Software Testing, Wireless Sensor networks, and Information Security."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Ms. CHINMAI SHETTY's departmental responsibilities?",
        "answer": "Ms. CHINMAI SHETTY's departmental responsibilities include being the Departmental Placement Coordinator, Departmental CSI Coordinator, Cultural Coordinator, NIRF Coordinator, and International Collaboration coordinator for the academic year 2023-24."
      },
      {
        "question": "What professional memberships does Ms. CHINMAI SHETTY hold?",
        "answer": "Ms. CHINMAI SHETTY is a member of CSI and IFERP."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which subjects has Ms. CHINMAI SHETTY handled?",
        "answer": "Ms. CHINMAI SHETTY has handled subjects such as Python, Graph Theory, Operating Systems, Computer Networks, Data Communication, Computer Concepts and C Programming, Data Structures, Logic Design, Software Testing, and Information And Network Security."
      },
      {
        "question": "What conferences/CME/workshops has Ms. CHINMAI SHETTY participated in?",
        "answer": "Ms. CHINMAI SHETTY has participated in numerous workshops, including those on Effective Teaching/learning of computer programming, LAB VIEW, Software Testing Lab, FDP in Teaching Pedagogy, Intel College excellence program, Network simulation using NS-3, Mobile Application Development, Nitte Open Source international Conference, FDP on Machine learning, workshop on Therapeutic Counselling for teachers in Higher education, and more."
      },
      {
        "question": "How many B.E. and M.Tech projects has Ms. CHINMAI SHETTY guided?",
        "answer": "Ms. CHINMAI SHETTY has guided 20 B.E. projects and 2 M.Tech projects."
      },
      {
        "question": "What additional information is available about Ms. CHINMAI SHETTY?",
        "answer": "Ms. CHINMAI SHETTY is a member of the Board of Studies for the course PGDCA in St. Aloysisus College, Mangaluru. She has been involved in organizing various workshops and events. Her project named 'Smart Waste Management System' was selected for funding by KSCST in the year 2016-17. She has also been recognized as a BRONZE partner faculty under the Inspire-The Campus Connect Faculty Partnership Model in the year 2018."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Ms. ALAKA ANANTH's educational qualifications?",
        "answer": "Ms. ALAKA ANANTH is currently pursuing a Ph.D. She holds an M.Tech(Research) in Computer Science and Engineering from NITK Surathkal (2015) and a B.E in Computer Science and Engineering from JNNCE, Shivamogga (VTU) (2012)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is Ms. ALAKA ANANTH's past experience?",
        "answer": "Ms. ALAKA ANANTH has worked as a Lecturer at NIE, Mysore from 30th July 2014 to 20th June 2017 and as an Assistant Lecturer at NITK, Surathkal from 21st July 2017 to 14th May 2018."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Ms. ALAKA ANANTH's areas of interest?",
        "answer": "Ms. ALAKA ANANTH's areas of interest include Cloud Computing, Data Structures and Algorithms, Computer Networks, and Natural Language Processing."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is Ms. ALAKA ANANTH's achievement?",
        "answer": "Ms. ALAKA ANANTH has participated in various events including chess tournaments, international conferences, workshops, and faculty development programs. She organized a Faculty Development Program (FDP) titled 'Quality research empowered by R and LATEX' (QuaRTEX) in June 2016 at NIE, Mysuru."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Ms. ALAKA ANANTH's departmental responsibilities?",
        "answer": "Ms. ALAKA ANANTH's departmental responsibilities include being the NSS Coordinator, Consultancy Project In-charge, Students Achievements Coordinator, Research Co-coordinator, Course File incharge, VISTA Co-coordinator, and Students Achievements Coordinator."
      },
      {
        "question": "What professional memberships does Ms. ALAKA ANANTH hold?",
        "answer": "Ms. ALAKA ANANTH is a member of IFERP."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which subjects has Ms. ALAKA ANANTH handled?",
        "answer": "Ms. ALAKA ANANTH has handled subjects such as Computer Concepts and C Programming, Data Structures using C, Probability Modelling and Simulation for Computer Science, Computer Graphics and Visualization, Discrete Mathematical Structures, Operating System, Digital System Design, Cloud Computing, Information Storage Management, Design and Analysis of Algorithms, and Web Services."
      },
      {
        "question": "What conferences/CME/workshops has Ms. ALAKA ANANTH participated in?",
        "answer": "Ms. ALAKA ANANTH has participated in workshops on PLC Based Programming and Automation, Understanding our adolescents, Suicide Prevention and Introduction to Therapeutic Counselling for Teachers & administrators in Higher Education, Data Science with Machine Learning and Python using Jupyter Notebook IDE, NPTEL Certification Programming with C++, Coursera Certification for various courses, NVIDIA DLI Certificate, AICTE Incorporating Universal Human Values in Education, FDP on Mobile App Development and Artificial Intelligence with MIT App Inventor, Online Webinar Series on Cyber Security, Workshop on Natural Language Processing and Deep Learning Techniques, and more."
      },
      {
        "question": "What additional information is available about Ms. ALAKA ANANTH?",
        "answer": "Ms. ALAKA ANANTH has been a resource person for a technical talk and demonstration on 'Report writing using LATEX' organized by ISTE student chapter. She has also received grants under various schemes and organized workshops."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Ms. PREETHI SALIAN K's educational qualifications?",
        "answer": "Ms. PREETHI SALIAN K holds an M.Tech in Computer Science & Engineering from NMAMIT, Nitte (VTU, Belgavi) in 2014 and a B.E in Computer Science and Engineering from St. Joseph Engineering College, Vamanjoor (VTU, Belgavi) in 2011. She is currently pursuing a Ph.D."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is Ms. PREETHI SALIAN K's past experience?",
        "answer": "Ms. PREETHI SALIAN K worked as an Assistant Professor Gd-II in the Dept. of ISE, NMAMIT, Nitte from 2nd September 2021. Previously, she served as an Assistant Professor in the Department of Computer Science & Engineering at Srinivas University College of Engineering and Technology, Mukka, from July 2014 to July 2021, and as a Lecturer in the Department of Computer Science & Engineering at St. Joseph Engineering College, Vamanjoor from October 2011 to June 2012."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Ms. PREETHI SALIAN K's areas of interest?",
        "answer": "Ms. PREETHI SALIAN K's areas of interest include Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Digital Image Processing, and Computer Vision."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is Ms. PREETHI SALIAN K's achievement?",
        "answer": "Ms. PREETHI SALIAN K was awarded a gold medal for scoring the highest marks in the MTech (CSE) course from NMAMIT, Nitte during the period 2012-2014."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Ms. PREETHI SALIAN K's departmental responsibilities?",
        "answer": "Ms. PREETHI SALIAN K's departmental responsibilities include being the NSS Coordinator and Alumni Co-coordinator."
      },
      {
        "question": "What professional memberships does Ms. PREETHI SALIAN K hold?",
        "answer": "Ms. PREETHI SALIAN K's professional memberships include having a SCOPUS ID - 57874793700, ORCID ID - 0009-0006-0320-9549, and a Google Scholar profile."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which subjects has Ms. PREETHI SALIAN K handled?",
        "answer": "Ms. PREETHI SALIAN K has handled subjects such as Machine Learning, System Software and Compiler Design, Automata Theory and Computability, Programming in C and Data structures, System Modeling & Simulation, Electronic Circuits, UNIX & Shell Programming, Programming the Web, Embedded Systems, Computer organization and Architecture, Database Management System, Logic Design, Compiler Design, Automata Theory and Computation, Software Engineering, Software Testing, and Programming in C."
      },
      {
        "question": "What conferences/CME/workshops has Ms. PREETHI SALIAN K participated in?",
        "answer": "Ms. PREETHI SALIAN K has participated in various workshops and faculty development programs including those on Machine Learning, Entrepreneurship, Innovations and Digital Skills, Artificial Intelligence, Deep Learning Applications, Data Analytics and Machine Learning, among others."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Mr. KRISHNARAJ RAO's educational qualifications?",
        "answer": "Mr. KRISHNARAJ RAO holds a DCS in CSE from NRAMP Nitte in 2005, a B.E in CSE from NMAMIT Nitte in 2009, and an M.Tech in CSE from Srinivas Institute of Technology (VTU) in 2013. He is currently pursuing a Ph.D."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is Mr. KRISHNARAJ RAO's past experience?",
        "answer": "Mr. KRISHNARAJ RAO worked at St Joseph Engineering College Vamanjoor, Mangaluru from 2021 to August 2022, and at Srinivas School of Engineering, Mukka, Mangaluru from 2013 to August 2021."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Mr. KRISHNARAJ RAO's areas of interest?",
        "answer": "Mr. KRISHNARAJ RAO's areas of interest include Image Processing, Network Security, Internet of Things, Machine Learning, and Artificial Intelligence."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Mr. KRISHNARAJ RAO's departmental responsibilities?",
        "answer": "Mr. KRISHNARAJ RAO serves as the Time Table coordinator and ACM coordinator."
      },
      {
        "question": "What professional memberships does Mr. KRISHNARAJ RAO hold?",
        "answer": "Mr. KRISHNARAJ RAO holds memberships in IEEE and ACM."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which subjects has Mr. KRISHNARAJ RAO handled?",
        "answer": "Mr. KRISHNARAJ RAO has handled subjects such as C Programming, Computer Organization, Java Programming, Analog and Digital Electronics, Embedded System Computing, Advances in Operating System, Information Network Security, Cloud Computing, Internet of Things, Software Engineering, Logic Design, and Unix Shell Programming."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Mr. KRISHNARAJ RAO's conference/journal publications?",
        "answer": "Mr. KRISHNARAJ RAO has a SCOPUS ID - 57220890883, ORCID ID - 0000-0002-2119-046X, WOS ID - AEU-0241-2022, and a Google Scholar profile."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Ms. ANUSHA N's educational qualifications?",
        "answer": "Ms. ANUSHA N holds a Ph.D. (Pursuing), an M.Tech. in Computer Science & Engineering from NMAMIT Nitte in 2017, and a B.E. in Computer Science & Engineering from NMAMIT Nitte in 2015."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is Ms. ANUSHA N's past experience?",
        "answer": "Ms. ANUSHA N has been working as an Assistant Professor Gd-I in the Dept. of ISE at NMAMIT since June 15, 2017."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Ms. ANUSHA N's areas of interest?",
        "answer": "Ms. ANUSHA N's areas of interest include Artificial Intelligence, Bioinformatics, Data Science, Image Processing, and Machine Learning."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Ms. ANUSHA N's departmental responsibilities?",
        "answer": "Ms. ANUSHA N serves as the Department Library Coordinator and Cultural Coordinator."
      },
      {
        "question": "What professional memberships does Ms. ANUSHA N hold?",
        "answer": "Ms. ANUSHA N is a member of IEEE."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which subjects has Ms. ANUSHA N handled?",
        "answer": "Ms. ANUSHA N has handled subjects such as Python Programming, Java Programming, Unix & Shell Programming, Linux Internals, Object Oriented Programming with C++, Object Oriented Modeling and Design, Software Engineering, Software Testing, Web Technology, Computer Networks, and Internet and Web Programming."
      },
      {
        "question": "What conferences/CME/workshops has Ms. ANUSHA N participated in?",
        "answer": "Ms. ANUSHA N has participated in several workshops, including those on Machine Learning, Web Technology & its Applications, NVIDIA Artificial Intelligence / Deep Learning, and more."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are Ms. ANUSHA N's conference/journal publications?",
        "answer": "Ms. ANUSHA N has a SCOPUS ID - 57211640401, ORCID ID - 0000-0003-4805-5687, and a Google Scholar profile."
      }
    ]
}
